

# **UX Designer**

fredkim.design fredk@alumni.usc.edu 714.975.1607

## **SKILLS**

Design	Tools	Languages	Research
Wireframing	Sketch	HTML5	Usability Testing
Prototyping	InVision	CSS3	User Surveys
Brand Creation	Illustrator	Javascript	Competitive Analysis
Content Strategy	Figma	jQuery	Storyboarding

#### **B** PROJECTS

#### **Skylake** - Cloud Sharing app

Skylake is a cloud redesigned for a faster, cleaner, and more intimate collaboration experience. It directly addresses the competition's four biggest problems - tedious navigation, ambiguous UI, feature bloat, and cluttered workspace. The solution comprises of minimal UI, one-click navigation, organized architecture, and global accessibility of features.

#### Fourth Wave - Coffee Discovery app

Fourth Wave curates artisan coffee blends, gear, cafes, and tutorials for aficionados who have no digital medium. It bridges the business-consumer gap with qualitative insight and elegance.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Bloc - UX Design Apprentice**

Jul 2018 - Feb 2019

- Apply user-centric & process-driven design under leadership of two UX professionals.
- Test and iterate through Lo-Fi/Hi-Fi prototypes with InVision, Sketch, & Illustrator.
- Build cross-platform and responsive interfaces with HTML5, CSS3, and Javascript.
- Empathize user needs via surveys, personas, stories, flow charts, & test feedback.
- Create brand identity with logo design, type selection, & style guides.

#### **Booz Allen Hamilton - Strategy Consultant**

Feb 2016 - Jun 2018

- Designed regional website, created career guides, and managed training for 250+ staff.
- Created requirements, information architecture, and install plan for \$10 million project.
- Managed client base of 150+ government representatives (Air Force, Army, & Navy).
- Supported GPS business & marketing with monthly budget status and executive resumes.

## **EDUCATION**

University of Southern California - B.S. in Mechanical Engineering Aug 2011 - May 2015

• Design for User Experience, Computational Solutions to Engineering Problems

Certifications: ICAgile Certified Professional, Certified SolidWorks Associate